你好，你们这些漂亮的人。
Hello you beautiful people.
欢迎回来，我们将继续讨论find命令以及如何控制
And welcome back we're going to be continuing our discussion of the find command and how we can control
搜索深度。
the search depth.
find命令也会进行搜索。
The find command searches too.
因此，如果我打开我们的文件Explora，我已经创建了几个新文件夹。
So if I open up our file Explora I've made a few few new folders.
所以在我们的Documents文件夹中，我创建了一个名为Level 2的文件夹。
So in our documents folder I have made a folder called Level 2.
在里面我有一个叫文本的文件。
And inside there I've got a file called to text.
然后是一个名为Level 3的文件夹，它要么是我有一个名为3的文件，然后他实际上就是Level
And then a folder called Level 3 and it's either I've got a file called 3 that he actually then Level
4表示4.6州5级，5.10 60表示结束。
4 for 4.6 state level 5 and 5.10 60 where it ends.
好的，我们将用这个来看一下如何控制搜索深度
OK and we're going to be using this to take a look at how we can control the search depth that the find
命令搜索也是如此。
command searches too.
所有这些内容都在我们的Documents文件夹中，您可以看到这里我将更改为我们的文档
So all of that stuff is in our documents folder and you can see here I'm going to change into our documents
文件夹，然后使用ls，您可以看到其中有Level 2。
folder and use an ls and you can see that level 2 is in there.
这就是我们现在看到的情况。
So this is what we're seeing at the minute.
这就是我们目前所处的情况。
This is what we are currently in.
就像我说的，把屏幕上的泥土粘起来，然后开始讨论。
Like I said Clay the screen and start a discussion.
如果我只是从这里运行find命令，find命令将进行无限深度的搜索。
If I just run the find command from here the find command will search to an infinite depth.
它将列出每个文件和每个文件夹。
It will list every file and every folder.
从文件系统中的这一点开始。
From this point in the file system.
好的，从这里到下面，如果我运行那个，你会看到它显示了2级，它会显示我们所有的东西
OK so from here and downwards so if I run that you'll see it shows us Level 2 and it will show us everything
在里面。
inside there.
所以你会看到我们最多到60级，它显示3级3.6 16级4.6级5和5.20所有级别
So you'll see we get to up to 60 and it shows a level 3 3.6 16 level for 4.6 level 5 and 5.20 everything
都显示在那里。
is shown in there.
但是我们也可以通过使用最大深度选项来控制来吧搜索的深度。
But we can control the depth of the come on searches too by using the max depth option.
那么让我向你们展示一下我们是如何做到这一点的。
So let me show you how we do that.
因此，如果我们键入find，我们将再次从当前工作目录开始，我们实际上可以指定
So if we type find We're going to again start from our current working directory we can actually specify
顺便说一句，为了让它更清楚一些，请记住，点就是这个目录。
that to make it a bit clearer by using the dot by the way remember dot means this directory.
实际上，从现在开始我将使用这一点，我将总是以说“好的，从…开始”开始。
So I'm actually going to use this from now on I'm just going to always start by saying OK start from
此目录中使用圆点。
this directory by using the dot.
好的。
OK.
因此，最大深度选项您键入1破折号，然后输入最大深度，您可以在此处指定深度，因此让我们
So the max depth option you type 1 dash and then max depth and you can specify the depth here so let's
比方说我们把1。
say we put 1.
你可能会注意到的第一件事是齐亚德，为什么这只是你长篇大论中的一小部分呢？
So the first thing you might notice is Ziyad Why is that just one dash of what you said for long form
选项。
options.
这些有两个破折号。
These have two dashes.
嗯，那就对了。
Well that's right.
但是对于有限的金额，你对这些选项只有一次冲刺。
But for the finite amount you only have one dash for these options.
好的，因为他们中的很多人都有这么多的长表格选项，所以我猜他们试图通过以下方式来节省您的打字时间
OK because so many of them the so many long form options I guess they tried to save you typing by just
把它缩小到一段距离。
reducing it to one dash.
好的。
OK.
所以我们在这里，我们只有一个破折号最大深度，然后是一个，这是最大限度的研究
So here we are we have just one dash max depth and then one and this is say on research to a maximum
深度为1。
depth of 1.
真的。
Really.
所以如果我们看到这一点，我们就会看到会发生什么。
So if we see that we'll see what happens.
您在这里可以看到，我们只看到Level 2文件夹。
You see here that we only see the level 2 folder.
因此，最大深度为1就像您在这里看到的一样，它只显示当前目录中的内容。
So a max depth of 1 is just like seeing what you see here it only shows you what is in the current directory.
好的，如果我做的最大深度是2，那就像是告诉你们这里是什么，下面一层是什么。
OK now if I do max depth of two that's like showing you what's here and what's one level down.
好的，如果我们看一下这里，我们应该看到的是第2层，然后它就会进入里面
OK so if we if we take a look here what we should see is we should see Level 2 and then it will go inside
它会显示2.6T。
and it will show you 2.6 T.
我是Level 3文件夹，因为如果我们运行MuxTape必须到Level 2，这是它显示给我们的
I'm the level 3 folder because if we run that Muxtape have to level 2 which is here it's showing us
Level 2文件夹。
the level 2 folder.
我们从这里开始让幕府将军进入2级沃尔达。
This is where we start shoguns level 2 Walda going in there.
她上到了60级和3级。
She goes to the up to 60 and level 3.
因此，我们可以看到Level 2文件夹设置为60，Level 3设置为Level 3。
So we see the level 2 folder to 60 and level 3.
好的。
OK.
现在，如果我们想要达到最大深度3，它将再下一层进入3层。
Now if we want to go to max depth of three that's going to go down another level into Level 3.
好的，对于拉玛，我们会看到三个带T级的，也就是图中所示的4级文件夹。
Ok so for Rama we'll see that we see three that takes T level the level 4 folder shown as well.
如果我们继续深入下去，我们最多能做到四个。
If we keep going deeper we do Max up the four.
我们现在开始看一下Level 4内部，我们看到的是4.6T和Level 5文件夹。
We're now starting to take a look inside level 4 we're seeing 4.6 T and the level 5 folder.
如果我们做MUXTAPE 5，它会一直往下走，直到我们看到5.6。
And if we do Muxtape the 5 it's going to go down even further all the way until we see 5.6.
你可以给它一个最大深度100，它仍然可以工作，因为你所定义的
And you can give it like you know a max depth of 100 and it will still work because all you're defining
是最大深度。
is a maximum depth.
好的。
OK.
这并不意味着它会一直走到那一步。
It doesn't mean it will go all that way.
如果可能的话，这就是它所能做的最远的事情了。
That's just as far as it could go if it was possible.
默认情况下到达那里。
Get there by default.
而且没有最大深度。
And there is no maximum depth.
所以它会把这里的所有东西都列出来。
So it will list everything here.
如果你想一直走进工厂，我们不需要指定最大深度，但是如果你
We don't have to specify a maximum depth if you wanted to go all the way into the factory but if you
想限制它走多远，那就是当你使用最大深度选项时，你说，嘿，我只想要你
want to limit how far it goes that's when you use the max depth option and you say hey I only want you
让我看看这个文件夹里有什么。
to show me what's in this folder.
这就是你使用最大深度1的时候，它对于列出当前的内容是令人难以置信的有用的
That's when you use max depth of one and it's incredibly useful for listing out what's in the current
文件夹。
folder.
现在，如果我们只清除屏幕，那么find命令还有另一个非常棒的选项，即
Now if we just clear the screen there's another really great option that the find command has which
是类型选项。
is the type option.
因此，如果我们只返回到这里的文档，类型选项允许您搜索
So if we just go all the way back up to our documents here the type option allows you to search for
仅文件或仅目录注意默认情况下，find命令列出文件和目录
just files or just directories notice by default the find command lists both lists both files and directories
但是您指定的类型只有一个。
but the type that you specify just one.
如果我从这里开始，在我们的Documents文件夹中列出从今年秋天开始的所有内容，您会看到我们
So if I start here and in our documents folder I list everything starting this fall you see that we
列出文件夹及其文件。
list out the folders and their files.
但是如果我说OK，我只想列出文件，我所做的就是键入类型选项，并再次注意
But if I said OK I just want to list out the files what I do is type the type option with again noticing
只有一次冲刺。
just one dash.
如果我只想要文件，我会键入f，f，file。
And if I just want files I would type f f file.
好的。
OK.
如果我现在按Enter键，你们会看到我们只得到4.6乘5.6乘3.6 D和2.6。
So if I press Enter now now you'll see that we just get 4.6 take 5.6 take 3.6 D and 2.6.
我们只要拿到文件就行了。
We just get the files.
同样，我可以通过按键来获得文件夹，而不是让f有D。
Likewise I could just get the folders by pressing instead of having f have D.
就像我说的，如果我键入D，你知道，当我刚得到文件夹的时候，所以级别2文件夹级别3文件夹级别4
Like I say if I type D you know when I just get the folders so level 2 folder level 3 folder level 4
文件夹和5级文件夹。
folder and the level 5 folder.
好的。
OK.
从这里的这个目录开始。
Starting at this directory here.
好的。
OK.
当然，您可以将此选项与最大深度选项相结合。
And you can combine this of course with the max depth option.
好的。
OK.
所以如果我现在做最大深度1，我们要做的就是最大深度1，然后显示
So if I do max depth of one now all we're doing is we're going to a maximum depth of 1 and just showing
文件夹。
the folders.
我故意这样做是想告诉你们，如果你把它们放在这里，你会得到警告，
Now I did this on purpose to show you that if you put them this way around you'll get a warning and
它会警告您已在非选项参数类型后面指定了最大深度选项，但在选项之后指定了最大深度选项
it says warning you have specified the max depth option after a non option argument type but options
不是有位置的。
are not positional.
好的，我马上告诉你这是什么意思。
OK I'll tell you what this means shortly.
真的很快。
Really quickly.
好的，这意味着把最大深度放在第一位。
OK what this means is just put max depth first.
这就是你要做的。
That's what you've got to do.
然后那个警告就消失了。
And that warning goes away.
因此，如果您要指定多个选项，请将最大深度放在第一位(如果可以，如果我清除
So if you're going to specify multiple options you put the max depth first if I could if I clear the
屏幕上，您将看到该警告消失。
screen you'll see that warning goes away.
所以我搜索到了最大深度1，并显示了所有目录。
So I was searching to a maximum depth of one and showing all the directories.
最大深度为2米。
That's go to a maximum depth of two.
当我看到Level 3文件夹的这个最大深度时，假设深度不是42max，共4个i
When I was seeing the level 3 folder for this maximum depth for let's say not 42 max depth of four I
看到三种类型，最多三种，我们将进入第三级。
see three types of the maximum of three we're going to level three.
我们看到的是第四级折叠起来，如果我们进入第四级文件夹，我们会看到第五级
And we're seeing the level four fold up and if we go into the level four folder we'll see a level 5
文件夹，如果我们进入5级，进入5级，也不会有什么不同，因为所有这些都在
folder and if we go into the level 5 go to Level 5 it won't make any difference because all that's in
级别5是另一个没有显示的文件，因为我们要查找的只是目录的OK。
Level 5 is another file which isn't being shown because all we're looking for is directory's OK.
所以如果我把它改成F..。
So if I go and change that to an F..
现在您将看到我们列出了所有文件，并且它的工作方式完全相同。
Now you'll see we list all the files and it works exactly the same.
这些都是非常好的组合选项，您可以做的事情有很多
So these are really good options to combine together and there's loads of things that you can do to
自定义Find命令实际搜索的方式。
customize the way that the find command actually searches.
但是，简单总结一下，type选项有两个可能的输入，您可以为file指定F
But just to quickly summarize that the type option has two possible inputs you could give a F for file
或D表示目录。
or D for directory.
如果您要将其与find命令一起使用。
And if you're going to use it with the find command.
请确保首先为其指定最大深度选项。
Make sure that you give it the max depth option first.
好的。
OK.
如果你要指定从哪里开始。
And if you're going to specify where to start from.
如果我们要在ETSI文件夹中执行此操作，我将列出每个单独的文件
Make sure that comes as well so if we're going to do in ETSI folder I'm going to list every single file
在SC文件夹中。
in the SC folder.
比方说，但仅限于最大深度1。
Let's say but only to a maximum depth of 1.
原来你在这儿啊。
There you are.
这是ETSI文件夹中的每个文件。
This is every single file that is in the ETSI folder.
你只要清空屏幕就可以了。
And you just clear the screen and do that.
这是没有任何目录的每个单个文件MenC文件夹。
This is every single file MENC folder without any directories.
如果我们只想查看目录，那么它们就在这里。
And if we just want to see the directories then here they are.
所以这是一个非常有用的命令组合。
So that's a very useful combination of commands to have there.
它在你们的作业中会非常有用。
And it will come very useful in your assignment.
所以我要把这段视频放在这里，让它保持漂亮，简短，甜蜜，下一段我们要播放的视频
So I'm going to break this video here keep it nice and short and sweet and the next video we're going
您可以使用find命令来获取一些更棒的功能。
to pick up with some more awesome stuff you can do with the find command.